[{"answer": "Most important to Elizabeth were her family, her friends, her care about AIDS research, standing up before anyone that we knew of in Hollywood stood up after her friend Rock Hudson died a terrible death from AIDS.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "What was most important to Elizabeth, do you think?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, I remember when I first saw her, everybody wanted to look like -- well, not -- when I first saw her, when she did \"A Date with Judy' when she was about 15 and everybody -- all my friends, all of us at school, we all wanted to look like her.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "I mean you've been a star the length of the time that she was, but there was something special about Liz Taylor, wasn't there?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "She was so giving and when she supported you -- if she liked you -- you had no better friend.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Did you love doing that play?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "AYLOR: Oh, wonderful.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Because that -- that -- that's top of the crop writing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "He was a brilliant actor.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "How did you like -- was Richard a helpful actor?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, I don't throw it often --", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Is that still the ring he gave you?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "No, it was like a couple of years later.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Was this his engagement ring to you?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Because of the -- first of all, Piers, you've never seen eyes like Elizabeth Taylor's.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "What made her that?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Same as she was on camera.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "What was she like?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "ING: Sure are, and even though she -- we didn't see much of her the last couple of years, she was very ill, we'll never have anyone -- think of it from --", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "I think the world is going to miss Elizabeth Taylor, isn't it, Larry?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Which I thought was incredibly sweet.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Did she really?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What was the real Elizabeth like, do you think?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I know what he thought.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "And what did you think that your father ended up thinking about Elizabeth?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, I mean she glowed.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "What was your impression of her as an actress?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, I think I always call it sort of rampant empathy.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "What was it about her that enabled her to have that empathy, do you think?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "She was this incredibly vital -- and she had a great, great sense of humor.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "How would you like the world to remember Elizabeth Taylor?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Truth!", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Why are you afraid of the truth?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Now, I don't think it was a risk for her because she has had all the strength and the courage and the dedication to do what she was doing, that nobody could touch that.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "She had two effects.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "What tangible effect did she have to improve people's live, do you think?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "That was the way it was supposed to be.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Getting angry, Betty?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "My favorite memory is totally unlikely.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Dick, what's your favorite memory of Elizabeth Taylor?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, there was just something so special about her.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110326pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Do you feel like today we've really lost a generation?", "qSentId": 511}]